anime-sub.com 2010-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Watch Privacy Policy Episodes Sub Online

## Privacy Policy

May 4th, 2009 

Game advertisements by [Game Advertising Online](http://www.game-advertising-online.com) require iframes.

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.  
\- Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on site.  
\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)

Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact me through my contact form or send me an email to: animesub@yahoo.com

**Every your review comment will help our site and others very much.Thanks for your contribution.Every report comment will get deleted after i fixed episode.You can report dead link on forum,it will better**
